Hilda Mason, Board of Education 136
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - Public Hearing on the Status of the Board of Education and the Organization and Administration of DC Public Schools, 1975 (Box 192, Folder 35)
  - Statement of John E. Warren - member D.C Board of Education, 1975 (Box 192, Folder 36)
  - Statement of Mrs. Virginia Morris - President D.C Board of Education, 1975 (Box 192, Folder 37)
  - Karen Henderson-Dorman Committee Speech, Undated (Box 192, Folder 38)
  - Statement of Hilda Mason July 3 1975 (Box 192, Folder 39)
  - Report on the Public Hearing on the Status of the Board of Education, 1975 (Box 192, Folder 40)
  - Public Hearing on the Status of the Board of Education, 1975 (Box 192, Folder 41)
  - Tenth Legislative Meeting, 1977 (Box 192, Folder 42)
  - Special Report on Bill 2-19 - the Accountablity in Public Education Act of 1977 (Box 192, Folder 43)
  - Gonzaga Student Correspondence, 1977 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - DC Government Merit Personnel Act of 1978 Correspondence, 1980 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Second Regular Meeting Committee on Education Recreation and Youth Affairs, 1977 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Advisory and Learning Exchange Spring - Summer, 1980 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Parents - Children Protest School Budget Cuts, 1980 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - 2-W Correspondence, 1979 (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Principal Rebuked in Ward 4, Undated (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Budget Correspondence, 1980 (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - FY 1980 Supplemental Request for Board of Education (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Operations Research: A Black Ghetto's Research on a University, 1970 (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - Follow Through Program, Undated (Box 193, Folder 11)
  - Condensed Follow Through Program Approaches, Undated (Box 193, Folder 12)
  - Legislation to be Filed, 1980 (Box 193, Folder 13)
  - Parents United for Public School Funding, Undated (Box 193, Folder 14)
  - DC Youth Orchestra Concert, 1980 (Box 193, Folder 15)
  - Real Property Inventory Summary as of Aug. 22 1980 (Box 193, Folder 16)
  - Oakland Public Schools, Undated (Box 193, Folder 17)
  - Berkeley Alameda Map, 1963 (Box 193, Folder 18)
  - The Rappin' Pape - Produced by Dewey High Art Class, 1973 (Box 193, Folder 19)
  - Words and Meanings, Undated (Box 193, Folder 20)
  - Hard Time Press, 1932 (Box 193, Folder 21)
  - Dewey High School Course Outline, Undated (Box 193, Folder 22)
  - Victor's Guide - Martin Luther King Jr. Elementary School, Undated (Box 193, Folder 23)
  - The Librarian and The Purchasing Agent - The Librarian vs The Purchasing Agent - Which Should it Be?, Undated (Box 193, Folder 24)
  - Your Child and Busing, 1972 (Box 193, Folder 25)
  - Release of Public Knowledge and Busing Opposition: An Interpretation of a New National Survey, Undated (Box 193, Folder 26)
  - Total Cost Components for the Fort Lincoln New Town Secondary School System, 1973 (Box 193, Folder 27)
  - Educational Program Recommendations for Fort Lincoln New Town Secondary School, 1973 (Box 193, Folder 28)
  - Facilities Performance Requirements Site Recommendations and Specifications for Fort Lincoln New Town Secondary School, 1972 (Box 193, Folder 29)
  - Fort Lincoln New Town, 1972 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - An Evaluation of the 1973-74 Emergency School Aid Act (ESAA) Projects in the District of Columbia, 1975 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Home Economic Curriculum Guide, 1970 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1980 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - Delegate Handbook for Delegate Assembly Workshop and Delegate Assembly Business Sessions, 1973 (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - Delegate Handbook for Delegate Assembly Workshop and Delegate Assembly Business Sessions, 1972 (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - NSBA Proceedings of the Seventh Annual Washington Meeting of the NSBA Council of Big City Boards of Education, 1974 (Box 194, Folder 7)
  - Extra ( 1 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - Extra ( 2 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Extra ( 3 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - National School Board Assocaition Research Report, 1975 (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - Report of 1975 Policies and Resolutions Committee (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - Survey of Public Education in Nation's Big City School Districts, 1975 (Box 195, Folder 6)
  - A Nine Weeks Unit on Individualized Instruction, 1974 (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - Students and Teachers Develop English Curriculum, 1974 (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - A Playwright Unit for Tenth Grade, 1973 (Box 195, Folder 9)
  - A Learning Package on Identifying the Parts of Speech, 1973 (Box 195, Folder 10)
  - Judding Other - A Unit for Tenth Grade Students, 1973 (Box 195, Folder 11)
  - A Unit on Discussion Skills, 1974 (Box 195, Folder 12)
  - First Love: A Writing Unit For Valentines Day Time Tenth Grade, 1974 (Box 195, Folder 13)
  - A Learning Package on Identifying the Parts of Speech, 1973 (Box 195, Folder 14)
  - Effective Usage, 1973 (Box 195, Folder 15)
  - Projects: Students and Teachers Develop English Curriculum, 1975 (Box 195, Folder 16)
  - Kinship and Society Notes, Undated (Box 195, Folder 17)
  - Eugene Kinkle Jones, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 18)
  - Maria Montessori, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 19)
  - Jewish Immigration to the United States from Central and Europe Between 1881-1924, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 20)
  - History of Transportation, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 21)
  - Dr. Martin luther King Jr. Bio, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 22)
  - The History of Medicine, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 23)
  - Three Waves of Germans to America - The Why the When and the Effects, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 24)
  - The Prophesies Being Fullfilled Today, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 25)
  - Adoptees in Search of their Natural Parents, Undated (Box 195, Folder 26)
  - Funding Inquiry for Research of American History and Expansion, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 27)
  - United States' Certificate of Birth, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 28)
  - Alexander Solzhenitsyn: His Life in Russia, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 29)
  - Lyndon B Johnson - A Picture Portfolio, 1975 (Box 195, Folder 30)
  - The History of Satire, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 31)
  - The Founder of the AME Church, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 32)
  - Malcolm X Bio, Undated (Box 195, Folder 33)
  - Martin Luther King, Undated (Box 195, Folder 34)
  - Maternal Grass Root: A Story of the Cragun Family, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 35)
  - Humor, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 36)
  - The Role of Women in the Theatre, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 37)
  - John Adams: A Man of Integrity, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 38)
  - The Origins of Jews from 1654 to 1812, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 39)
  - My Puritan Heritage, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 40)
  - The Ancestors of John Edwards Murphy, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 41)
  - A Packet of Vocabulary Games Developed and Used by Title III Students, 1975 (Box 195, Folder 42)
  - Classroom - Tested Curriculum Ideas Teaching Critical Thinking Making Inferences, Undated (Box 195, Folder 43)
  - Department of English - Goal Progress Sheet, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 44)
  - A Nine Weeks Unit on Individualized Instruction, 1974 (Box 195, Folder 45)
  - Haiku, 1975 (Box 195, Folder 46)
  - A Writing Lab, 1975 (Box 195, Folder 47)
  - Problem of Evil, 1975 (Box 195, Folder 48)
  - Improving Writing Skills: An Individualized Study Unit, 1974 (Box 195, Folder 49)
  - Designing and Implementing Little School Component ESEA Title III Evaluation Final Report, 1973 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Title III ESEA- Evaluation Special Education Projects Final Report, 1971 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Title III ESEA - Evaluation Special Education Projects Summary Report, 1971 (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - Charet Status of Dental Health in the Black Community, 1972 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Adams Morgan Brochure, 1976 (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - Council 20 AFSCME AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - Student Transportation, 1975 (Box 196, Folder 7)
  - Sizemore Hearing, 1975 (Box 196, Folder 8)
  - Statement of the Washington Teachers' Union ALF-CIO, 1976 (Box 196, Folder 9)
  - Mailing List, Undated (Box 196, Folder 10)
  - NASSP Bulletin - Bicentennial Edition, 1976 (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - Alternative Education, 1972 (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - African American Perspectives Pamplet, 1976 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - Hilda Mason Correspondence Rec'd Log Jan 1976- March 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - An Interdisciplinary Course of Study for Grades Seven and Eight, Undated (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - Teachers Manual for the Career Development Curriculum Guides - 7th and 8th Grades, Undated (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - Teachers Manual for the Career Development Curriculum Guides - 7th and 8th Grades, Undated (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - Hospitality Recreation and Personal Service Occupations, Undated (Box 197, Folder 8)
  - An Interdisciplinary Course of Study for Grades Seven and Eight, Undated (Box 197, Folder 9)
  - Agri-Business - Natural Resources Marine Science, Undated (Box 197, Folder 10)
  - Construction and Enviornment, Undated (Box 197, Folder 11)
  - Consumer and Homemaking, Undated (Box 197, Folder 12)
  - Public Service Occupations, Undated (Box 197, Folder 13)
  - Communications and Media, 1972 (Box 197, Folder 14)
  - Sizemore, 1975 (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - Superintendent Evaluation Instrument, 1973-1975 (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - Committee of the Whole on Personnel Meeting - May 31 1975 (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - Documentation Pursuant to the Notice of Proposed Adverse, 1975 (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - Board of Education v Barbara A. Sizemore Propsed Termination of Contact, Undated (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Sizemore Court Cases, 1975 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Sizemore June 1975 (1 of 3) (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Sizemore June 1975 (2 of 3) (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Sizemore June 1975 (3 of 3) (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - Board of Education of DC vs. Barbara A. Sizemore Matter of Proposed Adverse Action, 1975 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Board of Education of DC vs. Barbara A. Sizemore Matter of Proposed Adverse Action, 1975 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Public School of DC - The Language Arts Vol. A, 1969 (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - Public School of DC - The Language Arts Vol. B, 1968 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Current Organizational Structure, 1974 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - FY 1975 Authorized Positions - General Fund, 1974 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Vacancy Lists, 1974 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Motions - Committee of the Whole Personnel August 7 1973 (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Special Board Meeting, 1973 (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Copies of Reports and Excerpts of Minutes when Board Took Action, 1972 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Education and the Law, 1971 (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - A Teaching Strategy: Brotherhood, 1973 (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - The SIU Newsletter, 1972 (Box 201, Folder 8)
  - Experiences in Poetry Creative Writing of Students, 1973 (Box 201, Folder 9)
  - Greenery - Roper Junior High School Newsletter, 1973-1974 (Box 201, Folder 10)
  - Greenery Newsletter, 1971-1973 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Experiences in Poetry, 1973-1974 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Adventures with Words - Carvery School Newsletter, 1972 (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - A Financial Management Revolution, 1974 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - A Teaching Strategy - Roper Junior High School, 1973-1974 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - The SIU Newsletter (1 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - The SIU Newsletter (2 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - Dietary Goals for the United States, 1977 (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - Design for Academic Excellence, 1971 (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - DC Home Rule - Advisory Neighborhood Councils, 1974 (Box 202, Folder 10)
  - The War for the Nixon Tapes - Newsweek, 1973 (Box 202, Folder 11)
  - The Career Opportunities Program Newsletter, 1973 (Box 202, Folder 12)
  - A Revision of Specific Objectives for Pupil Performance in General Mathematics Grades 7-9, 1971 (Box 202, Folder 13)
  - Report of the City Council's Economic Development and Manpower Committee, 1971 (Box 202, Folder 14)
  - Curriculum Kit, 1971 (Box 202, Folder 15)
  - DC Public Schools Vol III - Recommendations Regarding Organziation and Management Information, 1972 (Box 202, Folder 16)
  - DC Public Public Schools - Volumbe IV Action Memoranda Prepared During the Review and Evaluation of Support Systems, 1972 (Box 202, Folder 17)
  - Volume I - The Budget Formulation System, 1972 (Box 202, Folder 18)
  - Vol II - Review and Evaluation of Support Systems to Improve Management Effectiveness, 1972 (Box 202, Folder 19)
  - Soul Journey - A Magazine of Leisure, 1973 (Box 202, Folder 20)
  - Black Dollar Magazine, 1970 (Box 202, Folder 21)
  - D.C Congress - 1971-1973 Souvenir Edition, Undated (Box 202, Folder 22)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, 1973 (Box 202, Folder 23)
  - Journal - Conversations with Cesar Chavez George Wiley and Ralph Abernathy, Undated (Box 202, Folder 24)
  - Staff - Names and Addresses, Undated (Box 202, Folder 25)
  - Handwritten Notes - Misc., Undated (Box 202, Folder 26)
  - States and Capitals of the United States of America, Undated (Box 202, Folder 27)
  - Title III Project - Students and Teachers Devlop English Cirriculum, Undated (Box 202, Folder 28)
  - Reading in the English Classroom - Four Curriculum Packages Developed by the Title IV English Teachers, 1976 (Box 202, Folder 29)
  - Title III Project: Students and Teachers Develop English Curriculum, 1975 (Box 202, Folder 30)
  - Classroom - Tested Curriculum Ideas - Teaching the Novel When Books are in Short Supply, 1973 (Box 202, Folder 31)
  - Classroom - Tested Curriculum Idea - An Annotated List of Books that Students Recommend, Undated (Box 202, Folder 32)
  - Classroom - Tested Curriculum Ideas, Undated (Box 202, Folder 33)
  - Love and Hate in Literature - A Unit for Tenth Grade Students, 1975 (Box 202, Folder 34)
  - Health Activities Project Newsletter, 1976 (Box 202, Folder 35)
  - The Clearinghouse - National Center for Voluntary Action, 1970 (Box 202, Folder 36)
  - Career Education, 1971 (Box 202, Folder 37)
  - Elementary and Secondary Education - Statistics of Public Schools Fall 1970 (Box 202, Folder 38)
  - Statistics of Local Public School Systems Fall of 1969 and Staff (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Health Manpower Development Corporation, 1974 (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - United Way of the National Captial Area, 1974 (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - Commentary - Cooperative Accountablity Project, 1974 (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - Bicentennial Calender - 1975 (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - Roles of Participants in Educational Accountablity, 1974 (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - Getting Involved - Your Guide to General Revenue Sharing, 1974 (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - Gardens for All, 1973 (Box 203, Folder 8)
  - National School Boards Association Of Special Interest, 1974 (Box 203, Folder 9)
  - Statistics of Public Elementary and Secondary Day Schools Fall 1973 (Box 203, Folder 10)
  - Ford Foundation Annual Report - 1973 (Box 203, Folder 11)
  - William S. Rice, 1969 (Box 203, Folder 12)
  - National Sorority - PHI DELTA Kappa Beta Chapter, 1972 (Box 203, Folder 13)
  - Steps Toward Total Health, Undated (Box 203, Folder 14)
  - Health Manpower Development Corporation, 1974 (Box 203, Folder 15)
  - Project Enterprise - Information kit, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 16)
  - The Treatment of Sex Roles Brochures, Undated (Box 203, Folder 17)
  - Cut Out Letters - Numbers, Undated (Box 203, Folder 18)
  - Instant Insanity, Undated (Box 203, Folder 19)
  - My Life Can be Beautiful - Introduction of Careers to Intercity Youth, 1975 (Box 203, Folder 20)
  - Piaget Children and Number, Undated (Box 203, Folder 21)
  - Emberley's Little Drawing Book of Weirdos, 1973 (Box 203, Folder 22)
  - Early Childhood Education "It's Art? It's a Science?", 1975 (Box 203, Folder 23)
  - NAEYC Annual Conference 1976 (Box 203, Folder 24)
  - Evaluation of Educational Programs for Young Children, 1975 (Box 203, Folder 25)
  - America's Children, 1976 (Box 203, Folder 26)
  - America's Children, 1976 (Box 203, Folder 27)
  - Using A Child's Drawings as a Measure of His Readiness to Read, 1970 (Box 203, Folder 28)
  - Reading and Writing Through Art, Undated (Box 203, Folder 29)
  - The Role of The Family in Child Development, 1975 (Box 203, Folder 30)
  - Harry and the Jellyfish, Undated (Box 203, Folder 31)
  - Literature - Summer Writing Conference, 1967 (Box 203, Folder 32)
  - Learning Through Selected Symbols, 1976 (Box 203, Folder 33)
  - Multi-Racial and Multi-Lingual Books for Use in Any Classroom, Undated (Box 203, Folder 34)
  - Curriculum Bulletin: Contemporary Africa, 1975 (Box 203, Folder 35)
  - Early Childhood Curriculum Guide - An Experience Report, 1975 (Box 203, Folder 36)
  - Gary - Indiana Correspondence, 1976 (Box 203, Folder 37)
  - Afro- American Perspectives - A Teacher Education Series, 1975 (Box 203, Folder 38)
  - Secondary Health and Physical Education Curriculum, 1975 (Box 203, Folder 39)
  - Do Some New Things - Friends for Big Boy - Meet Sone New Friends and Big Boys Children's Books, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 40)
  - American Management Association Educational Strategic Planning, Undated (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Decentralization, 1974 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - The Council of the Great City Schools, 1972 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Support Report Academic Acheivement Plan (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Support Report Academic Acheivement Plan (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Julius Hobson Sr. Candidate Info, 1974 (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Ward IV Resident Correspondence, 1973 (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - Personnel Qualifications, 1973 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - English for the Seventies Levels 7-18 (1 of 3), 1971 (Box 204, Folder 9)
  - English for the Seventies Levels 7-18 (2 of 3), 1971 (Box 204, Folder 10)
  - English for the Seventies Levels 7-18 (2 of 3), 1971 (Box 204, Folder 11)
  - Child Growth in the Middle Grades, Undated (Box 204, Folder 12)
  - Profiles in Quality Education, 1968 (Box 204, Folder 13)
  - Toward Better Schools, 1967 (Box 204, Folder 14)
  - Title III ESEA State Plan, 1974-1975 (Box 204, Folder 15)
  - ESEA Title III McFarland - Truancy ( 1 of 2), 1975 (Box 204, Folder 16)
  - ESEA Title III McFarland - Truancy ( 2 of 2), 1975 (Box 204, Folder 17)
  - Title III NDEA, 1973-1975 (Box 204, Folder 18)
  - ESEA Title V-A WAE Positions and Tilte VI, 1973 (Box 204, Folder 19)
  - Mrs. Mason Title IV Handicapped, 1974 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - Civil Rights Act Title IV, 1976 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - Title III Open Space Training Center (1 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - Title III Open Space Training Center 2 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - Morse Crisis Intervention Center: Project Advance, 1975 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Montessori Preshool, 1972-1973 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Little School Component, 1975 (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - Learning Through Selected Symbols, 1974 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Instructional Development Agency Project, 1972 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - Junior- Senior High Tutor/ Aide Program at Malcolm X Elementary School, 1974-1975 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Students and Teachers Develop English Curriculum, 1972 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - Education and Services for School Age Mothers, 1973 (Box 206, Folder 8)
  - Mainstreaming, 1975 (Box 206, Folder 9)
  - Urban Enviornmental Education, 1975 (Box 206, Folder 10)
  - ESEA Title III Program the World is Your Museum, 1975 (Box 206, Folder 11)
  - Proposal for Division of Special Education Support Servcies Branch, 1974 (Box 206, Folder 12)
  - School Recycled: A Community-Based Program for Development Through the Middle Years, 1974 (Box 206, Folder 13)
  - Proposal to Involve Parents/Administrators/Community Residents/Students in Educational Planning and Goal Setting, 1974 (Box 206, Folder 14)
  - ESEA Title IV Part B, 1976-1977 (Box 206, Folder 15)
  - ESEA Title III - State Plan for FY 1976, 1975 (Box 206, Folder 16)
  - Extended Services for Blind and Visually Impaired Older Americans, 1974 (Box 206, Folder 17)
  - Project Inspire ESEA Title III, 1974-1975 (Box 206, Folder 18)
  - Street Law - A Course in Practical Law, 1974 (Box 206, Folder 19)
  - Final Evaluation Report - 1971-1972 Institute for Educational Development, Undated (Box 206, Folder 20)
  - Staff Development Institute for Educational Development, Undated (Box 206, Folder 21)
  - ASBSD Bulletin, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - WTOP A Post - Newsweek Station The Right Decision in the Yeidell Situtation, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - WEAL Washington Reoprt - Women's Equity Action League, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - Hawkins Full Employment Bulletin, Undated (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - Pamplets and Brochures, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - Urban Affairs/News/Views of the NSBA Council of Big City Boards of Education, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - Committee of 21 and Interested Citizens - April 25, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - Literature Curriculum, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - WAEYC Newsletter - 1977 (Box 207, Folder 9)
  - Banking for Non- Bankers Conference Agenda, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 10)
  - Parent Dissatisfaction Correspondence, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - Focus on Exceptional Children, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 12)
  - The American School Board Journal, 1976 (Box 207, Folder 13)
  - Houston Report '77 37th Annual Convention, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 14)
  - Daily Talk - Today's Black News, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 15)
  - 1973 Captial Outlay - Budget as Presented to House Appropriation Subcommittee 4/20/72, 1972 (Box 207, Folder 16)
  - Answers to Budget Questions July 17 1975 (Box 207, Folder 17)
  - Head Count Back Up Materials, 1972 (Box 207, Folder 18)
  - Mutli Year Program and Financial Plan Fiscal Years 1973-1977, Undated (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Boundary Reporr for, 1972 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Theodore Roosevelt and Rabaut Junior High School Promotion Exercises, 1977 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Louis Stokes - black Appointees to the Charter Administration Invitation, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - Revision of Section 482 of the Rules of DC Board of Education, Undated (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Position Papers, Undated (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - Closing Exercising for Grade 6 Rudolph Elementary School, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - Community Gram, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - Draft Position Paper - Committee of Concerned Faculty and Student Body of Antioch College, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - Ward III Board Community Meeting June 1 1977 (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - Conference on New Directions in State and Local Tax Reform Invitation, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 9)
  - Big Cities Survey: "Role of Board Members and Superintendents", 1977 (Box 209, Folder 10)
  - Cityscape - A Journal of Urban Life, Undated (Box 209, Folder 11)
  - Interested Citizens of Vocational Education Correspondence, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 12)
  - Focus on Execptional Children Newsletter, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 13)
  - Benefit Cocktail Party for the Willis Quads, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 14)
  - Vincent E. Reed Correspondence, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 15)
  - Dwight S. Cropp Correspondence, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 16)
  - Therman Evans Correspondence, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 17)
  - Press Release 4/1/77 DC School Board Members Active in National School Boards' Meeting, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 18)
  - Bell Pollard Collection, 1976 (Box 209, Folder 19)
  - How City Hall Shortchanges the Schools, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 20)
  - Board of Education Vacancy Bill, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 21)
  - Widening Horizons, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 22)
  - Title 4500 - Grants/Gifts/Donations Government Policy for Initiating and Obtaining Grants from Federal Agencies, 1972 (Box 209, Folder 23)
  - School Calender - Vacations and Holidays Statement of Hilda Howland Mason, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 24)
  - Public Law 86-725 86th Congress HR 7124 September 8 1960 and Amendments, 1968 (Box 209, Folder 25)
  - Va Public School Newspaper Articles, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 26)
  - Paperwork Management Program - Disposition Personal Papers and Official Records, 1976 (Box 209, Folder 27)
  - Reassignment of Displaced Officer Personnel, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 28)
  - Bill 2-19 Correspondence, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 29)